Call me that smile
Good morning, good afternoon, whatever time it is
wherever in this vast world it is that you may or may not be, welcome once more to another live
stream of IRL Neustime Live. I'm your host Alexandra. Alexandra, hopefully this transmission
will come through effectively. I'm in a very remote location as of current, so the internet's not so
But I'm going to do my best to bring forth the information for those of you who listen to me for the right reasons.
Before we get started.
Let's do a little bit of the Palin Flinzer.
Oh please no.
Some music.
Please no.
No.
Why he defaulted into some sort of false narrative about me wanting his sperm.
as a nefarious party known as the son of Judy
has chosen to paint a false narrative,
which we are going to go ahead and go over right now.
I do specialize in helping to rehabilitate
people who are viewed as lost causes.
Oh!
Successful, right?
When it comes to females, not males.
But it's possible Brandon might be the first. I want to make it clear
I have zero communication with Brandon in no way
I know am I defending him if anything he will continue to become
Incredibly angry with me and curse me to kingdom come. Oh, that's part of the plan, right?
But that's to my and his benefit. Oh, I'm right
is to others detriment.
Oh.
Because any kind of help,
they cannot have romantic attachment to me.
It has to be strictly business.
Dickly, dickly.
Completely platonic.
And that has not been the case with several
I've tried to help who are male,
whether they deem themselves as truly being hetero or not.
But what I will say,
is that I will not tolerate being lied about
when it comes to my intention.
I will not tolerate-
There's bad intentions about me.
I will not tolerate people telling fairy tales.
I will not tolerate legally actionable slander.
So let's start with this.
Apparently, this was posted earlier today, and it is going to be forwarded directly to Riviera Center Management.
I think it seems like I have to floor with you, bitch.
As will all the live streams and content relative were related to this situation.
Approximately eight hours ago, and again, I'm basically time traveling right now, so I don't know if eight hours ago is accurate or not.
This was written by the son of Judy Bates and
Daelos Bates. It's important to note that this individual has stated
publicly
that Daelos Bates is not indeed his father's name. So what does that mean?
Okay, I want to pause real quick. Is it illegitimate child? No, it means
his mother was essentially my grandfather's name. The definition of what I worked professionally as?
for many years but behind closed doors unknown to me but anyway let's read
this oh Alexandra I'm not saying that you change your mind like a goldfish with
ADHD look at that pop calling the kettle black
black color the pedal already told me things like you know I'm not bald with
the face like Cyrax well actually you are bald and I ball you guys I'm all
the time is moving fast the ball here for you son of Judy Basin my bald head
guys every day for you is essentially a month oh my god and that you may that
art to test my attention months ago oh my god never said that
You also asked if I would give you my sperm
True oh, she begs as many of you have noticed have your calm the son of Judy
I'm here to have a genetic disease something along the lines of what Eugena Cooney has
Cooney you have a coon bitch. You don't make coon in addition. He already has mental
Degenerative I have that
Keep this straight
Much of anything that in conjunction with his substance abuse issues
Sorry, it's going to lead to a fairly early grief for him. Okay, please give me out of this world
If you went and exactly how you wanted me to give it to you
I'm not you said you said you wanted me to fuck her. I told you I'm flattered, but not interested in you that way
I don't remember any of them. I've never stated any of this
This is all a fairy tale that I would assume was lifted from Tommy James fairy tale
Oh, please. I don't steal fairytales. I'm sorry to me now. I already have a genetic contributor
Who does not like the
Reading that post up very much. Look at this. It's worth it. I would suggest that the individual who wrote that post
Apologize
Who is absolutely real
I want to see what the genetic
According to plan I might have seen some really good news today. Actually, you know, what is the genetic?
Christine is very aware
That this individual that you're seeing on what the fuck is that real?
This is an AI
Interpretation of the individual but from a distance. We have a great waist looks exactly
Like that. See someone like that coming. What is that?
And you've had issues with me you might want to do a 180 and run the other way. Oh my god scary
But let's continue
Though, you know at one time I would have done anything to make you happy now. That's a weird thing to say
Like I would have given a rent spurred. You have a baby. Is that made her happy? That's what I said
That's very strange
You send it
Only that on one occasion to say that they would have done anything to make me happy. Yeah
Gross the whole thing alludes to something that was not it's weird. Okay, again, this is a very
Really fancy fall kind of
person who does need a professional. Here comes the truth guys, truth bombs. When they continue,
but hey, looks like Good Times is still interested. Who is this person referring to?
Maybe Good Times. Good Times for life, AK. Oh, that's it. You're a smart guy. Me and I are just
online acquaintances. Who's Good Times? I would not even say friends. Who's Good Times? Every once
in a while, we have a conversation.
about 80s in Stalshaw.
80s in Stalshaw.
So that's weird.
Okay, okay, okay.
Then he continues, we can never be together.
Good!
So leave me alone. I think you leave me alone. I mean my family alone you fucking bitch. Hold on to leave me alone
Leave me the fuck alone bitch. I forgot they have no content. Oh, I forgot your content to me for the past weeks
We're ready for their malicious and criminal stalking and harassment. Oh, please you're stalking me
You fucking suck everybody nothing to do with it. We're all getting a class action
When it comes to young
boys possibly to do with him. Oh, I actually feel at this point these communities might deserve
the kind of monster that this fool is. I know. Time to get over my quote Jesus with a side of Jared
Well, I don't know what that means.
Oh, you don't?
I'm looking at, now I am a fan of Jared Leto,
but this person looks very decrepit.
Oh, oh, I looked to crepe it, right, bitch?
I looked to crepe it.
Oh, what, what is, what, what do you mean?
Jesus was Jared Leto.
Oh, should we just take a time machine back a couple months
when she first hoovered me?
Let's go have a look at that and see who Jared Leto
plus Jesus is, because it's certainly with me.
But let's look into it. Let's look into it. No, there's not going to be on video actually saying that exact phrase
There's no way right because she doesn't remember
She doesn't remember well either means she's a big drunk
With a memory problem
Or she's making shit up
Let's have a look at it. Let's just have a look though. Okay, and the toothpaste is out of the tube with everything
So, you know here and I'm not afraid of the bitch, okay? Everyone else
You're gonna be afraid of the bitch, okay?
Listen, listen my children or whatever you are my adults get behind my cloak. Okay. I
Have this woman's kryptonite. Trust me
Probably in my semen, but okay. I digress. Okay. Hold on a second
Let's hear a little bit of the of this woman that doesn't like me that I'm just so here's the first time the first Hoover
Are you ready?
You want to hear the Hoover? You want to hear her say?
verbatim Jared Leto
We can do it.
That's what footage is for.
That's why I save this.
This is my show, okay?
Let's hear it, let's hear it.
Let's hear her hate me, okay?
Let's hear, oh, do you want to hear it if you give me in?
And say I'm sorry, I was wrong?
Resease, yes, we're gonna receive right now.
Let's do it, we're gonna receive right now.
We're gonna do it for it.
Hold on.
Also beautiful at this moment. I probably look really fucked up to be honest with you a little bit at the cross-eyed
Trump up mean it better than me. Like I look like I just rolled out of bed, don't I?
Yeah, but you're a guy. It's different
It's different you look like Jesus Christ meets
A modern day, I don't know, Jared Leto, Rockstar, kind of vibe.
Whoa!
Thank you.
Yeah, my hair is pretty much the same point as I've ever been.
It's like...
I haven't cut it since it's probably too many.
It's not that long.
Yeah, it really is.
It's got the little curly cues and whatnot, don't you?
Yeah, I wish it like came out like, you know, it's just beautifully straight.
Maybe I can do that later.
Well, no, no, not straight.
I like the curliness.
If anyone comes up on the stream and I don't want to talk to them and let you know right
now, I'm going to depart.
I want your help.
With what?
With a selfish matter.
What, you want me to spur him?
Okay.
Well, I don't even know privately.
Yeah, you should.
Okay.
Or maybe publicly, what it is.
My loneliness is killing me, because it is.
I didn't realize that till today.
But it is.
And that's why I'm so grumpy.
The North's gonna protect me, by the way.
Yeah, but I'm pretty grumpy too, you know.
It is, I'm like, I've been alone like a lot of my life,
like just like, you know, on my own, like, you know,
kind of even like with everybody or even with people around
kind of like alone, you know, like I'm alone.
Are you?
No one's gonna lie a little bit.
You're less lonely than me, I would say.
Well, I have these cats and so the cats, like, there's three cats.
Well, did tricks, what happened with tricks?
Tell me the tricks update, because I've been worried about that.
My followers know that.
Yeah, well, it's tricks, it's tricks back, like, where's tricks?
Tricks has not come back.
Okay.
And I have a, you know, a notice in the next door with a really good photo of him.
He has a distinct illegal freckling on his nose and stuff, which is like, we'll make it easy to identify.
Well, he's the gray striped cat, right?
He's a gray cat.
Anyway, I'll put a picture of him.
Let me see.
I have a picture of him.
This is a picture.
Yeah, put a picture.
Because, yeah, because, I think you're thinking of his mom, like Lola, like, um, she's like, um...
Oh, what an idea.
Is that what it is, John? Is that what it is?
It is a little bit...
Yeah, I mean, I just like, it's like...
I don't think any things that I've done actually happen in issue, to be honest with you.
But, um...
Okay.
What are you gonna do, Psyche?
I'm going to keep calling you John. You're going to hate me for it, but that's who you
are to me at this point. You're Mr. John. And I like calling you John because you look
like a John. And hey, and I mean, I've been a prostitute, sex worker, legal, legal, legal,
legal. So maybe you're my, you know, eternal John forever, even though I've never been
We are certainly platonic friends. Oh, you guys throw up Lenore
Okay, Lenore my spirit animal I suppose
Defending you from
Is that what it is?
Realize that over the past few years your sexual energy
Well, you know, let me let me let me put you on my
Channel cult of psyche. What why are you tracking me into your cult which I'm not necessarily opposed to what was going on with your ass?
well, it's like I
know
But I was going to call the cult of two and like, you know
Well, I did like it, but it's like he's nightmares. That's what you're calling it. The nightmares really I'm looking at it right now
nightmares on Elm Street
Really really really really maybe on the lane of street. Oh
Okay, uh-huh
Maybe
Look, I'm gonna be the real asshole in your life
You know, you want to be LGBTQ? Okay. Well, let's let it be. I'm gonna be the asshole that exists in that world
You know, I'm not really well no matter what I'm born into that world
That's what you just pissed me off about your friend ghost really didn't you hear my own
Rant about that
I listened to that, I listened to two episodes, kind of like the rant, but it wasn't really a rant, it was really a rant.
I'm sorry.
Oh here, apology, apology.
She apologized for the first time she fucking fucked me over.
I don't think the work is-
I put you through hell, didn't I?
If we're paying attention to each other and like watch you and like stuff, but do it again
I'm publicly acknowledging it right now you you put me through some stuff, but I do what I do you I'm
What did I do you? I'm sorry. I should have been born a male
in a wartime, probably two generations ago.
I would be very good at it.
Yeah.
I'm sorry.
But you're so funny.
I'm just thinking, oh, you're sorry, thank you.
Thank you so much.
I am.
I'm very sorry because I have all this.
And it's a weapon, and it shouldn't be, but it is, but I'm sorry, because I had to beat
you down a little bit, sorry.
I'm sorry, but you survived. I did. I did. I did. I did. I did. I did. I did. I did. I did. I did. I did. I did. I did. I did. I did. I did. I did. I did. I did. I did. I did. I did. I did. I did. I did. I did. I did. I did. I did. I did. I did. I did. I did. I did. I did. I did. I did. I did. I did. I did. I did. I did. I did. I did. I did. I did. I did. I did. I did. I did. I did. I did. I did. I did. I did. I did. I did. I did. I did. I did. I did. I did. I did. I did. I did. I did. I did. I did. I did. I did. I did. I did
You didn't deserve
I didn't and I still don't yeah
I got a little bit ugly, but I have to like learn how to laugh at myself
You know even in the memes, you know, it's like I was I was like well
Like you're tough yourself. I mean beat the shit out of me man
I always want to like more like
You know feel like it's a friendly a friendly thing even like I know if there's public things going on like
It'd be like, at least like, to like, kind of like, be understanding, you know, otherwise.
Well, how are you going to be? Are you going to be cult of psych, or psychic awakening?
Because if you're going to be cult, I'm going to, I'm going to take over the cult for you to let you know right now.
Oh my gosh, well, I don't know if you're,
or did you see, did you see the Rajneesh video?
Oh, I don't know if it's up anymore.
You did not see it.
Like, it's a trippy kick, trippy kick made it.
And I don't know if you ever watched it,
but I don't know if it's new channel.
So, are you nervous?
Oh, the whole thing going on.
No, but I mean, it's in a different way.
Yeah.
In a different way.
I mean, I feel like I have to go up against,
what's that guy's name, Ghost?
He hates me, so I'm gonna have to completely obliterate him, but I love God or Goddy, that he's my favorite.
Oh, yeah.
So, I mean, how am I gonna destroy a cult from Goddy, or God is a part of it?
Well, let me try this. Maybe I can summon him. I'm not sure. I do have a means to like, you know, maybe like...
I want to know what he looks like so bad yet. I don't want to know because it's such a mystery.
And then I have a thing that is who can always pacify me.
Oh, God, it says it, Goddy, get over there.
Get the fuck over there, how do you know?
I know it's gonna be a brat.
Passify her, all of it.
Look, I know I'm not gonna be able to come back
on your stream the way I am right now for a long time.
Well, you were there.
But I'm just, I normally don't say I love people,
but I do love you.
Oh, wow.
Well, I love you too, and uh, I might not say it tomorrow
It was sometimes we do change from day to day with nothing's a promise nothing nothing's a story about anything, you know
It's like but for this moment. I do mean it today. Thank you
Flip it ship it. What are you guys doing? Thank you so much. Seriously. Thank you for permission
But I mean it at this very particular moment today. I love you very much
And if you ever said to me or anyone else that care about over I will destroy you
Well, I believe I believe that and you know, I will respect that and and that's a little it
with
See I
And that's like, I don't know. I might have been possessed. I knew she was little. I knew it. Did I call it? I called it. Oh, gosh
I didn't think about talking to Mr. Bigpipes way before I met you or like I think maybe
just after.
Well, you were talking about a lot of people that I've talked to before I knew about you
from what I've done in my own little miniscule research, so I'm actually surprised by that.
I definitely have been surprised by that.
Well, I have been like continuing to watch your show and it's like kind of it's not now
I like you know, I'm really liking the episode
I was worried about you all day today as you're you know, I'm not gonna say what I said to you privately or anything
But you you you're not allowed. Well, like the level that you're
present
Online you're not allowed to tell us when you're
Well, you have to give us notice when you're going to be MIA missing in action because
I was worried about you all day today.
There are certain people who are in these online communities who know that I was worried
about you all day today and you can't do that to us anymore.
Because I know that you sit there like, oh, nobody cares about me. I want to kill myself
You better not kill yourself. We all do care about you tremendously and you're a game-changer
You know people give you a hard time. They razz you they haze you whatever the term is that they want to utilize
but we do love you very much and
There's a video generation on there you can do and splicing stuff. I mean yeah, so that's really cool
I know did you did you go last night to that? I mean do you see the title of that show last night?
It was your name and stuff
I don't know yeah, I listened for like 10 minutes, and it wasn't really about me
It now we're gonna press today guys. I was like, okay. I'm really not what was there to listen to
I don't think it wasn't a summoning you said she was summoning me so well
I thought I just saw your name and I said God and then I went back and read it
It's like oh Gotti
Yeah, I just thought it was odd that I was even mentioned. But what was the point? Yeah?
I don't know if you saw the very beginning
I didn't hear I did see a little like she meant to mention like you a little bit like oh
You know God like there's she mentioned like Alex and ghost and like as my friends and like these are people that to go out
I think that's what anyone anyone who associates with you. Yeah, you basically at this point
yeah that's whatever you know what can you do and then um but you know that then it gets into
the threats of physical violence and then also lying and stuff and also you know
Yes, her father passed away, you know, like that was the reason
like when we met was like, because my father had just died
like the year before, but when we met, it was just about a year
and a half, I guess. But and hers went like shortly after mine
like a year later. And so we both and I'm still grieving, you
know, it's like, and so, and I'm not like insensitive to people
grieving their family. I mean, it's that stuff doesn't go away.
Yeah, that stuff never goes away.
Two years for me. Yeah.
And so that's, I'm not saying she, but so it's, and then it's like, she's saying, I, I, uh, I asked her for, I pressured her into, I, I, all kinds of stuff, right.
And, um, and then started to, starting to get physical violence, and then Christine was like, well, you know what, no Jerry's going to convict you because, you know.
Um, you know, but look at his videos and see what a what a lunatic he is and I think it's just it's just the same
The whole thing went to this point. I mean you guys would have, you know, right? Oh my god
I mean and I got it. I yesterday I sent her a message and I was like what's in this now
I was like just take down the dog scene videos of my family and then I will
Um, you know or and I said like looking to your heart and then she's like, you don't know
It's in my heart like literally was like that's scary and then um and started yelling like she possessed
Someone said oh my god
Honestly, the only thing I can say the best thing would be to just fucking just leave it alone
Just leave it alone. Are you gonna listen to it with me or no?
Oh, yeah, I get two minutes. I get too much. I gotta take off. Go ahead. Go ahead. Okay, man. I need to put the banner up for one second
No problem. Thank you.
No problem.
She made threats on recording this.
Do you understand that I would theoretically be justified to do things that I never would do?
Yeah.
So I think he needs to stop immediately.
And those of you who are enabling and contributing.
If certain things come upon you leaving and that's what I'm saying to this asshole
known as Gotti trying to sit there straddling the thing that is too
I didn't realize that he was a kind of piece of shit that he seems to be. I thought well for and Christine knows
And he consistently keeps saying well, what if you didn't do this?
What if you didn't do that? Why can't you cut the cord?
And if you can't cut the cord, don't make it come negative upon me.
And if you can't do that, don't be surprised if things happen to you.
I already warned him once.
It doesn't just make warnings well, nor does he take leave me alone, which is very succinct
to the point.
Hey, uh, it's just like positive for a second, positive for a second.
Well, then that means that he needs to be succinct.
Got it.
Who's talking over the track?
Oh, that's, um, that's INX.
She's recording this for me.
Oh, she's recording it, um, but talking to herself and commenting on the track.
Yeah.
I because it's because she deleted the slide right after and so I know I knew she would. Oh, okay
I thought she was talking to you about the trucker. Okay. Yeah, go ahead
Personalized I've said that
Okay, I need me institutionalized and there's a lot of things that needs to be examined and that's why I consistently name the legal team of
Riviera center management in Riviera
Properties
Yeah
It's gonna go pretty far figure out what that means. Yeah, I think so. Um, I think so
And I know Alex, you know a little bit, probably more than I think you know about me, but I have four adult sons, four.
Let me tell you, Christy, I know that certain people have been like, oh, Alex is bashing Christy because she says that she would never be over.
My friend, what I define as friend, like friend.
personal circle, physical life, okay. I'm not saying, oh, if I were to ever encounter
Christine in person, I would not be your friend. That's not the case. But what I do know is
that you and I live very different lives. And I know that online is one thing. And I know
You know, there might be a chance, but I'm not saying that you're, I look up to the kind of person you are. You've raised from what you said, multiple children, you've worked in the healthcare industry successfully.
Yep.
You're, you're, to my knowledge in a relationship, I could be wrong, but I think so.
42 years.
42 years. Okay.
Better than what?
had five children, four sons, okay. She also she volunteered for hospitals, okay. She was an
official nurse. She volunteered in a hospital and everything that she's saying that she loves
Christina about, she attacks my mom, who she's never even met her. I think my mom remember
But let's listen to you.
If many people, I mean, your success story, okay?
Right, right.
You know what?
I would love to have your life.
I would love that.
I'm sorry.
Everything that you've seen is in there.
That's my mom's too.
that she's trashing, saying she's a bad person
because she raised a horrible son and stuff.
My mom's a mother.
My mom was a volunteer, actually, in hospitals.
And also, she was married for over 42 years, right?
And so, but that's a success for Christine,
but it's like, you know,
that my mom is just, you know,
she says horrible things about her
and just trashing her name.
Actually, my whole family, it's just terrible.
Yeah, it's like let me let me say this before I go. Let me say let me say I'm not taking any size in this
I'm not taking any side. You should got it because
I know I know I'm not saying anything negative about her
As the as a hurt person man, she feels like she was hurt by you. Okay. She's lying. She's lying. Whatever reason she has this is what she's doing
And she's laughing out. Yeah, but she's obsessed. She's preoccupied. All right
So if you if you both if you both continue to hurt each other, it's gonna always gonna
I haven't done anything to her. No, no, but but she perceives that she perceives what you're doing
That's all I'm saying. I'm not I'm not taking anybody's side. I'm just saying that body's had a naked side
All right
I can tire at this divide and conquer BS.
I'm sick and tired of all of them.
You need to use some payback, Alex.
Let's look at what's going to get AIDS.
The guy, what are dogs?
Well, I'm going to say, I have raised four sons,
and I think they are very good men.
And I'm going to tell you, I had a son, an act like psych.
Man, I would intervene to the point
if I had to go to court and get custodial care, I would.
Sure, his parents fucking tried that.
They're at the point where they threw him in a fucking
apartment and he wouldn't do it.
I'm figuring out why people in these communities
were really its only immature males don't like you,
because you are a white American woman who is successful
and you're a mother and they know damn well
they can't pull the wool over your eyes.
That's what it is.
Okay, they liked me for a while because I guess they thought I was Oprah Winfrey wrong
Okay
what really have to happen is state intervention because his family, I think he's blackmailed
and extorted his family. When I really think about the chain of events, I think about the whole
thing. I think that they're probably scared of him.
All I would be, that's what all I would ever be.
They threw him in the apartment and he told me to shut up and leave me alone.
This first time he's been exposed and I'm not afraid of his family.
I'm not afraid of the legal team.
I'm not afraid of any of these jackasses.
none of them. What true? To be honest, we should not be. No. And there's things coming
down the pipeline that he ain't expecting. He's going to have a hard time going to that
McDonald's in the future. He's going to have a hard time going to that liquor store in
the future. He's going to have a hard time going anywhere. He's going to have to move.
And then let's see how are you fairs?
Let's see, that's when you had to move with me.
I don't know why is one neighbor hasn't moved
in file chart for file, I'm lost.
You're an intimidation.
But here's what I'm gonna tell you.
I'm the kind of person who's capable of being a real bitch.
Oh yeah.
So you know what he considers his YouTube channel his job, so right
It's gonna be to the death. Oh
Not to the death. Oh, yes. Oh wow
Any very good ready death threats on a public plan to live a very long time
You better be careful. He's going to make a AI video about you like a song.
Let's go ahead and make some videos about who he alleges that he's related to in law enforcement.
My uncle? I can't believe that day he said that. I'm like, are you kidding me?
Wouldn't that be interesting. There's a lot of things.
Okay, if I were hip, I would move to a different platform, really, and go away.
Never.
I would just get off the social media.
I think it's time to get a traditional job when it comes in, right?
I'm obviously not working tomorrow, or today.
But I have a traditional job, as do the majority of us.
Or if you don't, you're likely retired, or there's a reason.
I'm not going anywhere.
But he doesn't have that reason.
And if he continues with me, he's not going to survive.
Okay
He seems to think he's untouchable and that has blown my mind over and you know he goes after the good people
Well know this
He does, other than Ghost and Alexander McQueen.
Yeah, and those two, along with the person
who's noted in the description or a title of the stream,
they might think that they're anonymous,
but what if they're not?
Threatening them too, huh?
Nobody's ever really anonymous, we know that.
No.
I think that it's time to go ahead and close.
the cult or whatever it is.
I was going to get my ass out of it.
You have been in this cult.
You're out, out.
Archie, let us know what that works for you.
Yeah, you know, no people.
Alex, maybe that's already happened.
I have AIDS now.
I have AIDS, okay.
Considering, yeah, I think it's possible
it's already happened with him.
But I don't think I don't think it's right that he's a drain on his family.
Come from a certain level of it and not near to the extent of him
But I've always worked part of the reason that I went into the adult entertainment and streak was because I didn't
Want to be a reliant upon my parents. Okay?
Okay, by the way, however it is that you want to
Talk about relying on their parents
So after she dropped out of high school and she got her GED
Then she dropped out of her first year of college and became a stripper and stuff like that
Then she moved back in with her mom and sister who couldn't fucking stand her and they kicked her out
And then she was living in her car. She's on the street holding a sign
There's pictures of that too then she moved in with her dad. Okay?
Talk about relying on your parents and then her father passed away and he left her some money
And now she's traveling around say whatever the fuck she wants. Okay, but she has things to say about me, right, right?
think that for him I've heard some things that he's had to say and I'm like
really you're gonna act like you were ever my quote-unquote friend but then
you're gonna say number one because you were mad at your dad that's exactly
what he said okay well then he does deserve a solid punch directly in the
face
That's what he deserves
I'm not saying I would ever do it
but here's what I would say
he needs to be careful
anywhere he goes for the rest of his life
Oh wow
What I will say is that
I have always taken care of myself
along with many others
and I've always been that kind of a person
I've always been generous. I was raised that way. I've always been empathetic, kind, compassionate to the best of my ability, but I've also been raised not to be taken advantage of. And that is where I have failed, not just myself, but my family over the past few months.
And I am ashamed of that. And for him to be coming at me in a time to where I am not 100%.
If he does ever cross my path, and I lose my fucking mind, and I knock the living hell out of him, I will be forgiven by the courts.
Because of the circumstances, and I'm very aware of this,
he needs to go ahead and disappear out of my existence immediately.
Zayden, don't...
He won't.
We know this.
No, then there will be repercussions, won't there be?
I remember you had words on his panel.
It was actually kind of funny.
He's played that like three or four times this week.
Oh my god
Regret that stream, but I was obviously well, here's the question. Why would you consistently play?
someone in a grieving
Oh, I'm obsessed. Okay. Next. I'm not ashamed when I am saying as I've obviously been grieving March 9th
Hand as he died in hospice. Okay. I've seen someone die in person
Let alone hold their hand let alone have them be there my best friend let alone them be my father
And if he's going to exploit that, yeah, if I see him in person, I'm going to kick his fucking ass!
You record this, you clip this, you take it to law enforcement.
I'm pretty sure, considering that I've never been arrested in my life,
that I'll get a slap on the wrist, and if not, fine.
Lock your door, psyche.
I think that he needs to stop.
I'm sorry.
And I hope to God that others learn from what the pain is that I'm obviously contending with.
I'm a pretty, look, if you have a woman.
Talking about me, 47 years old, went through hell and back, went to school for computer science.
I lost my job because our jobs were outsourced to India.
Went into the entertainment industry. Before that, the hospitality industry.
To be able to pay my own bills without my parents' assistance
Then went into the entertainment the adult entertainment industry because when I was young I was a hot little thing
I realized hey, but then I took it another level. I
Got a lot of girls out of the strip clubs onto
Being cam girls save them. Oh my god. Oh, thank you so much. You guys heard us in a porn stars from strippers
Great did great job, bitch
What's up? How's it going?
Hi, boyfriend.
How are you?
My best buddy.
Well, you know, it's 7-12 today.
Oh, what is that? Oh, a replenish.
It's like a...
Cherry lemonade. Yeah.
Cherry limeade, yum.
The second level B.
Are you drinking alcohol, though?
Oh, my God. You're drinking Chilada, I saw.
Oh, my God.
Okay, well you mind listening to a few minutes I listen to a few minutes of this and here I'll put us on
I'll put us on this put us on a side and make it small or something to figure it out
Let me get bigger
It's like this hold on here. We go listen to this. This is about me for lives and many
Oh, so now I'm a sex trafficker.
I'm peasy, I'm peasy, I'm peasy, come on.
No, actually you're not, you're an asshole.
Come on, I'm just joking around.
I'm trying to lighten up.
No, you're an asshole, but if you want to call me a pimp,
fine, strangely, I never had any of their income come to me.
I never took a cut.
I was one of the first black bar managers in the North Miami area when it came to exotic
dance or strip clubs, okay?
You don't even understand what I had to go through.
The guy who was my employer had to have a meeting with the staff because they wouldn't even accept me as being their, as being their boss. Okay.
Then I go into the adult entertainment industry as an adult actress. Nobody wanted to pay my rate. I had a manager who fought for me.
People are like, oh, she didn't have many films yet because I wasn't going to fuck for free. Okay.
I've been through hell and bad.
You wanna talk about things that have to do
with prejudice, racism.
People think I pulled the race card, not really.
Right now, race card.
Not considering what I've actually lived.
I mean, I get it.
You laugh it off.
You think it's funny.
Okay, fine.
God forbid, you be reincarnated into this body.
You wouldn't like it.
You mean the best of it?
You wouldn't, like, have a brain that I have, but the body that I have, you couldn't handle it, you would kill yourself, you would put a gun to your freaking head and you would blow your brains out, that's the reality.
Okay, shut the fuck up.
Come on now. I don't even want you on here. I'm taking you from the panel. I can't I can't deal with you
You lack everything you like
Telling you
I don't like it
I got to make one little joke.
No, it's not a joke.
This is my life.
And you're doing the best you can.
You don't.
She's better than a lot of other black women.
A lot.
You don't get it.
I don't want you on here.
I don't want you on.
I don't want him on.
And it took me forever to even get him off.
I don't hate him.
But I don't get it.
I have been far more gracious, far more classy, far more
Chicken.
It's fucking horrible.
You know, one of the problems that Black women face
is that we embody more pain and accept it
We just take it to where even health problems manifest and we don't pay attention to it.
It's my younger relatives who have brought this my attention.
And they have just from looking at my online presence, they're like, whoa, you actually went through a lot.
Are you okay? And I'm like, well, I'm still living, you know, when it comes to people like Bates.
I don't give a shit if I incur negative karma. I hope he drops dead. Okay. I don't think it's going to be negative karma.
I really hope he drops dead. I hope he drops dead. And that way it's over. I don't want anyone to kill him.
And that's very possible someday with the drug in alcohol is I think does I mean
I'm sorry Christine. I'm sorry. I didn't mean I
trust me. I go through a lot and sometimes it comes out. Okay, it goes because I
wasn't fucking around when I said thank you for being a friend like seriously I
don't want to thank you for being a friend also one more story
I was on the phone with her. I heard like that noise. She's like, oh, I'm sorry. I just farted
And when it was like what I mean, it was it was the most disgusting
It was like what what's just farted like the safe of marshmallow man
I mean, it was it was not a normal human being. It was like an extra system. It was I mean seriously
on that note
It's maybe a low note
But I'm gonna end
You guys heard it, but yeah, she said that that's what she said
And I was like, oh you're suddenly the evil out, but it kind of sounded like she's I mean, but oh my god
It was disgusting. It was disgusting or anything like in your life guys
Almost be the witness to this. I mean, I've heard the craziest fucking shit in your life
You cannot even just you can I even imagine
What I've heard from this woman and I get to quiet and I was very sweet
I was very sweet, and I was like, okay. This is my friend
But if you want to you want to play this shit with me, bitch, I'll play back. Okay, I'm gonna go
I'm gonna go hang out with one of my friends. Maybe we're gonna watch a movie and falls together. I do have real friends
But she's not a real friend. She was a fake person being a fake friend
What was she after? I don't know
And guys, on my life, I swear that that happened.
I wish I would record my phone calls.
You guys could have heard that.
It was like, it sounded like, okay guys,
we'll have a good night and thank you for listening
and have a wonderful night.
I'll play one more, I'll play my song on the way up.
Oh, hold on, we have a guest.
What, what, am I sick?
Or, bang, bang?
What's up, slut?
Let's have a say say if you're at a gay experience. I just want to find out before you go a gay experience. What in gay experience?
Every single every single experience that I've had
Has been gay. Yeah, okay single one
Okay, so say if you were farted and then blamed it on the evil spirits
Yes, regularly
Well, I mean that's the perfect that's the perfect note to end on do you want to see about that the star knows more
Before I leave or I'll just like leave you in here using our one the star knows mole wrap
What is it? What is the star knows more? Okay? You're in for a treat. You're in for a treat sick. Okay got it for you
Okay, you're ready for it. No, I'm gonna get on the screen sounds cool
I'm excited. Please tell me about it.
You're excited. I love it. I love it.
You know, it's sick. It's sick.
Sick. No matter what, you've been on my show
since the beginning. We had our differences and stuff.
But you've been here and you're a cool guy
and I appreciate you and if you hate me,
I do appreciate you and just thank you for bringing you, okay?
I don't hate you just like you.
Oh, you don't hate me?
No, I don't hate you either.
I don't hate you either.
Okay, I'm gonna play the roll round.
I think you hate me more than I hate you.
Well, maybe.
You're probably right.
If we put the gradient, we put this on gradients.
We're going to put it on gradients, whatever that means.
But I mean, OK, I have it ready.
Hold on.
True facts.
I'm hypothetically speaking.
OK, I got it.
Are you ready?
I'll just make a minute clip, and then I'll go, OK.
But this is the star.
It's sponsored by miniclip.com.
It is. It's started.
Okay, guys, miniclip.com.
Sit.
Say shout out your Rumble channel real quick.
It's streamed sponsored by rumble.com
slash real Alex Jones channel.
Okay, perfect.
Rumble.com slash real Alex Jones channel.
You're right. You're ready to see this.
I got it ready for us.
Okay, I got it ready.
Okay, here we go.
Now that you see it like that, I'm kind of like concerned.
No, don't be concerned.
Maybe I don't want to see it.
You do want to see it.
Watch this.
You ready?
I'm not sure.
You're ready, right?
You're saying it in a really weird way.
Hey, stay.
Let me just blow in your ear.
I'm going to blow in your ear once I get it.
Stay.
You want me to get a boner in my ear?
Yes, I do.
Here we go.
These are true facts about the Starno's Mole.
Holy crap, did you just...
The Starno's Mole is a mole that looks a bit like a plush toy that was squeezed too hard,
and whose insides are starting to come out one end.
It makes its home tunneling in soft, moist, marshy soil.
Oh god, stop doing that!
The Starno's Mole is a carnivore, but it is functionally blind,
and instead of sight, it relies on a remarkable adaptation.
It's tail. Just kidding. It's the nose.
Even though the star-nosed mole's nose looks like it snorted a firecracker up each of its nostrils
and then lit the fuse to the point where real stars are frankly offended by the comparison,
it is an astonishing sensory organ. However, this nose is less about smelling as it is about touching.
Each of its 22 nose tentacles is covered with thousands of tiny touch receptors called the
Are you kidding me? You wrote that in the script? Fine, I'll just make it up.
Tiny Touch Receptors called my writers an idiot and his wife Le- oh, Imre's organs.
You just say he old-
These Imre's organs can sense microscopic differences on the surfaces they come in contact with,
and because of this, the Stano's Mole is the fastest eating mammal in the world.
It can identify something as edible and consume it in as little as 120 milliseconds, which is this long.
To understand this, put on a blindfold and have your friend hold out an object in front of your mouth.
Now lick it and decide to eat it in this amount of time.
Sorry, you just ate a piece of cat poop. Try again.
No, that was a pencil, which he stuck in cat poop.
The star-nosed mole is constantly groping the world around it, up to 13 separate areas of the ground every second.
To the worm, the star-nosed mole's nose looks like a little worm orgy party.
And it's like a fella's mind if I join?
Oh, that tickles.
Like someone's using their teeth.
Oh, crap.
Little is known about its social habits,
but we do know that the star-nosed mole's testicles
swell up to 9% of its body mass during mating season.
If you were a 200-pound man,
that would be roughly the size of a bowling ball.
which would make it hard to ride a bicycle.
But the star-nosed mole doesn't ride a bicycle.
Remarkably, it spends much of its time hunting for underwater prey in streams and ponds.
That's a terrible transition, it made no sense.
It is one of the few mammals that can smell underwater,
blowing bubbles and inhaling them as it swims.
We have no footage of this, but get into a bathtub and try to sniff one of your bubbles.
Trust me, it's not easy.
If you ever thought your nose was too big, just remember, stop that.
Love you guys.
Just kidding.
Of course, we had the footage.
No, no, no.
This is the bdc ball.
They've got footage of the inside of your face.
Love you.